http://www.breakawaytours.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The information we request from you will enable us to provide you with the highest levels of personal service on every trip. We will not disclose any personal information to any external company or person without a traveler’s informed consent unless we are required by law to disclose this information.
With the growth of electronic media we recognize that it is necessary to take further steps to protect the privacy of the individual. We are compliant with the provisions of Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation and it’s regulations. We respond to requests or inquiries from potential travelers, referrals from our past passengers and organizers, and existing customer requests for information. We will also contact our existing travelers with information relevant to their currently-booked trip. For any other communications we send (like emails about future trips, newsletters, contests & giveaways) we will be sure to gain your consent prior to contacting you, and you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the ‘Unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of the email.
Our role in protecting an individual’s privacy does not stop with this Legislation. We maintain the security and confidentiality of the information disclosed by our travelers according to the strictest standards. We are continually looking for additional ways to ensure that the personal information we hold is secure and used in a responsible and respectful manner.
CONTEST ENTRANTS
By submitting your information to Breakaway Tours, contest entrants consent to the collection, use and disclosure of their personal information for the purposes of administering the contest and promotional purposes. The information we collect is used to track entries and is not shared or sold to third parties for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve won. In certain circumstances it may be necessary to share information with partners and/or suppliers in order to administer the prize to the winner. Entrant agrees to receive communication by email, phone or mail from Breakaway Tours in regards to products or services. Winners may be required to sign an affidavit of eligibility and release. Names and likenesses of winners may be used for promotional purposes without compensation.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  In the event of merger, acquisition or name change Breakaway Tours reserves the right to assign the terms of this Agreement to such new party. You may not assign this agreement without the written permission of Breakaway Tours.  We may use entrant information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. We may update this policy from time-to-time. To keep up-to-date with Breakaway Tours privacy policy, please check back here periodically.
PRIVACY QUESTIONS
If you have any questions or concerns about the Breakaway Tours Privacy Policy please give us a call at 1-800-465-4257.
Do You Love to Travel?
For over 30 years, Breakaway Tours has created extraordinary travel experiences for High School students. Our trips spread joy and spark an appreciation for travel, culture and friendship. A big part of our success is our knowledgeable, enthusiastic and hardworking team.
We're constantly growing, so if you're passionate about youth travel and want to join a group of like-minded people, we want to hear from you! Take a look at our job openings listed below.
Join Our Team
Providing the ultimate student travel experience for over 30 years.
